A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Public Health, SG 1, Series 12 FA284
Rockefeller Archive Center
- State Files, 2
  - New Jersey - General Correspondence, Memoranda and Reports, July 11, 1947-December 15, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 379)
  - New Jersey - General Correspondence, Memoranda and Reports, July 11, 1947-December 15, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 380)
  - New Jersey - Miscellaneous Brochures and Reprints, 1951-1953 (Box 25, Folder 381)
  - Ohio - Reports of Public Health Activities, 1930 and 1932 (Box 25, Folder 382)
  - Oklahoma - Ada - Correspondence and Reports, February 27, 1937-April 28, 1937 (Box 26, Folder 383)
  - Oklahoma - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, April 15, 1938-February 8, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 384)
  - Oklahoma - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, April 15, 1938-February 8, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 385)
  - Oklahoma - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, April 15, 1938-February 8, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 386)
  - Oklahoma - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, April 15, 1938-February 8, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 387)
  - Oklahoma - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, April 15, 1938-February 8, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 388)
  - Oklahoma - Clerical Training - Correspondence and Reports, February 1, 1944-April 1, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 389)
  - Oklahoma - Division of Laboratories - Annual Reports, June 30, 1941 to July 1, 1942; July 1, 1945 to June 30, 1946; and February 1948 (Box 26, Folder 390)
  - Oklahoma - Field Unit Annual Reports, 1944-1947 (Box 26, Folder 391)
  - Oklahoma - Field Unit Annual Reports, 1944-1947 (Box 26, Folder 392)
  - Oklahoma - Field Unit Semi-annual Reports, 1939-1943 (Box 26, Folder 393)
  - Oklahoma - Field Unit Semi-annual Reports, 1939-1943 (Box 26, Folder 394)
  - Oklahoma - Field Unit Semi-annual Reports, 1939-1943 (Box 26, Folder 395)
  - Oklahoma - Financial Correspondence, September 15, 1938-August 18, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 396)
  - Oklahoma - Financial Correspondence, January 21, 1942-March 3, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 397)
  - Oklahoma - Financial Correspondence, January 21, 1942-March 3, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 398)
  - Oklahoma - Financial Correspondence, January 21, 1942-March 3, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 399)
  - Oklahoma - Financial Correspondence, January 21, 1942-March 3, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 400)
  - Oklahoma - General Correspondence and Reports, April 20, 1937-October 22, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 401)
  - Oklahoma - General Correspondence and Reports, April 20, 1937-October 22, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 402)
  - Oklahoma - General Correspondence and Reports, April 20, 1937-October 22, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 403)
  - Oklahoma - General Correspondence and Reports, April 20, 1937-October 22, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 404)
  - Oklahoma - General Correspondence and Reports, April 20, 1937-October 22, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 405)
  - Oklahoma - General Correspondence and Reports, April 20, 1937-October 22, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 406)
  - Oklahoma - General Correspondence and Reports, April 20, 1937-October 22, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 407)
  - Oklahoma - Kay County - Correspondence and Memoranda, February 12, 1942-December 23, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 408)
  - Oklahoma - Kay County - Correspondence and Memoranda, February 12, 1942-December 23, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 409)
  - Oklahoma - Kay County - Correspondence and Memoranda, February 15, 1944-September 16, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 410)
  - Oklahoma - Kay County - Correspondence and Memoranda, February 15, 1944-September 16, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 411)
  - Oklahoma - Kay County - Correspondence and Memoranda, February 15, 1944-September 16, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 412)
  - Oklahoma - Kay County - Correspondence and Memoranda, February 15, 1944-September 16, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 413)
  - Oklahoma - Kay County - Evaluation Schedules, 1948-1949 and 1952 (Box 28, Folder 414)
  - Oklahoma - Kay County - Health Center Correspondence and Reports, June 22, 1949-November 2, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 415)
  - Oklahoma - Kay County - Health Center Correspondence and Reports, June 22, 1949-November 2, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 416)
  - Oklahoma - Kay County - Health Center Correspondence and Reports, June 22, 1949-November 2, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 417)
  - Oklahoma - Kay County - Health Center Correspondence and Reports, June 22, 1949-November 2, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 418)
  - Oklahoma - Kay County - Reports, 1943-1946; 1948 (Box 28, Folder 419)
  - Oklahoma - Kay County - Reports, 1943-1946; 1948 (Box 28, Folder 420)
  - Oklahoma - Kay County - Statistical Summaries, 1943-1948 (Box 28, Folder 421)
  - Oklahoma - Seminole City Health Center - Correspondence, December 12, 1947-May 5, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 422)
  - Oklahoma - Seminole County - Correspondence and Memoranda, June 29, 1938-November 29, 1941 (Box 28, Folder 423)
  - Oklahoma - Seminole County - Correspondence and Memoranda, June 29, 1938-November 29, 1941 (Box 28, Folder 424)
  - Oklahoma - Seminole County - Correspondence and Memoranda, January 22, 1942-July 6, 1949 (Box 29, Folder 425)
  - Oklahoma - Seminole County - Correspondence and Memoranda, January 22, 1942-July 6, 1949 (Box 29, Folder 426)
  - Oklahoma - Seminole County - Health Center Correspondence, April 24, 1947-January 9, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 427)
  - Oklahoma - Seminole County - Health Center Correspondence, April 24, 1947-January 9, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 428)
  - Oklahoma - Seminole County - Health Center Correspondence, April 24, 1947-January 9, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 429)
  - Oklahoma - Seminole County - Health Center Correspondence, April 24, 1947-January 9, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 430)
  - Oklahoma - Seminole County - Reports, 1938-1943; 1945 (Box 29, Folder 431)
  - Oklahoma - Seminole County - Reports, 1938-1943; 1945 (Box 29, Folder 432)
  - Oklahoma - Seminole County - Reports, 1938-1943; 1945 (Box 29, Folder 433)
  - Oklahoma - Seminole County - Statistical Summaries, 1941-1949 (Box 29, Folder 434)
  - Oklahoma - Statistical Service - Correspondence and Reports, November 20, 1944-September 16, 1948 (Box 29, Folder 435)
  - Oklahoma - Statistical Service - Correspondence and Reports, November 20, 1944-September 16, 1948 (Box 29, Folder 436)
  - Oklahoma - Statistical Summaries, 1921-1944 (Box 29, Folder 437)
  - Tennessee - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, November 14, 1929-June 25, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 438)
  - Tennessee - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, November 14, 1929-June 25, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 439)
  - Tennessee - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, November 14, 1929-June 25, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 440)
  - Tennessee - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, November 14, 1929-June 25, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 441)
  - Tennessee - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, November 14, 1929-June 25, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 442)
  - Tennessee - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, November 14, 1929-June 25, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 443)
  - Tennessee - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, November 14, 1929-June 25, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 444)
  - Tennessee - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, November 14, 1929-June 25, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 445)
  - Tennessee - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, November 14, 1929-June 25, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 446)
  - Tennessee - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, November 14, 1929-June 25, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 447)
  - Tennessee - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, November 14, 1929-June 25, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 448)
  - Tennessee - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, November 14, 1929-June 25, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 449)
  - Tennessee - Clerical Training - Correspondence and Reports, July 9, 1945-July 26, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 450)
  - Tennessee - Clerical Training - Correspondence and Reports, July 9, 1945-July 26, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 451)
  - Tennessee - Dental Hygiene Program - Reports, March 5, 1937-June 3, 1940 (Box 31, Folder 452)
  - Tennessee - Field Trip Reports, December 8, 1929-September 5, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 453)
  - Tennessee - Field Trip Reports, December 8, 1929-September 5, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 454)
  - Tennessee - Field Trip Reports, December 8, 1929-September 5, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 455)
  - Tennessee - Field Trip Reports, December 8, 1929-September 5, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 456)
  - Tennessee - Field Trip Reports, December 8, 1929-September 5, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 457)
  - Tennessee - Field Unit Quarterly Reports, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 458)
  - Tennessee - Field Unit Quarterly Reports, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 459)
  - Tennessee - Field Unit Quarterly Reports, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 460)
  - Tennessee - Field Unit Quarterly Reports, 1933-1938 (Box 32, Folder 461)
  - Tennessee - Field Unit Quarterly Reports, 1933-1938 (Box 32, Folder 462)
  - Tennessee - Field Unit Quarterly Reports, 1933-1938 (Box 32, Folder 463)
  - Tennessee - Field Unit Semi-annual Reports, 1939-1947 (Box 32, Folder 464)
  - Tennessee - Field Unit Semi-annual Reports, 1939-1947 (Box 32, Folder 465)
  - Tennessee - Field Unit Semi-annual Reports, 1939-1947 (Box 32, Folder 466)
  - Tennessee - Field Unit Semi-annual Reports, 1939-1947 (Box 32, Folder 467)
  - Tennessee - Field Unit Semi-annual Reports, 1939-1947 (Box 32, Folder 468)
  - Tennessee - Field Unit Semi-annual Reports, 1939-1947 (Box 32, Folder 469)
  - Tennessee - Field Unit Semi-annual Reports, 1939-1947 (Box 32, Folder 470)
  - Tennessee - Field Unit Six Year Report, July 1, 1930-June 30, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 471)
  - Tennessee - Financial Correspondence, March 16, 1931-September 28, 1942 (Box 32, Folder 472)
  - Tennessee - Financial Correspondence, March 16, 1931-September 28, 1942 (Box 32, Folder 473)
  - Tennessee - Financial Correspondence, March 16, 1931-September 28, 1942 (Box 32, Folder 474)
  - Tennessee - Financial Correspondence, February 22, 1943-April 6, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 475)
  - Tennessee - Financial Correspondence, February 22, 1943-April 6, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 476)
  - Tennessee - Financial Correspondence, February 22, 1943-April 6, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 477)
  - Tennessee - Financial Correspondence, February 22, 1943-April 6, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 478)
  - Tennessee - Financial Correspondence, February 22, 1943-April 6, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 479)
  - Tennessee - General Correspondence, Memoranda and Reports, April 4, 1928-September 27, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 480)
  - Tennessee - General Correspondence, Memoranda and Reports, April 4, 1928-September 27, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 481)
  - Tennessee - General Correspondence, Memoranda and Reports, April 4, 1928-September 27, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 482)
  - Tennessee - General Correspondence, Memoranda and Reports, April 4, 1928-September 27, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 483)
  - Tennessee - General Correspondence, Memoranda and Reports, April 4, 1928-September 27, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 484)
  - Tennessee - General Correspondence, Memoranda and Reports, April 4, 1928-September 27, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 485)
  - Tennessee - General Correspondence, Memoranda and Reports, April 4, 1928-September 27, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 486)
  - Tennessee - General Correspondence, Memoranda and Reports, April 4, 1928-September 27, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 487)
  - Tennessee - General Correspondence, Memoranda and Reports, April 4, 1928-September 27, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 488)
  - Tennessee - General Correspondence, Memoranda and Reports, April 4, 1928-September 27, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 489)
  - Tennessee - Gibson County - Correspondence
    - March 1, 1930-September 18, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 490)
    - March 1, 1930-September 18, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 491)
    - March 1, 1930-September 18, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 492)
    - March 1, 1930-September 18, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 493)
  - Tennessee - Gibson County - Health Center Correspondence, December 16, 1936-May 3, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 494)
  - Tennessee - Gibson County - Statistical Summaries, 1921-1946 (Box 34, Folder 495)
  - Tennessee - Gibson County - Yearly Report, 1929-1935; 1937; 1939-1940; 1943 and 1945 (Box 34, Folder 496)
  - Tennessee - Gibson County - Yearly Report, 1929-1935; 1937; 1939-1940; 1943 and 1945 (Box 34, Folder 497)
  - Tennessee - Gibson County - Yearly Report, 1929-1935; 1937; 1939-1940; 1943 and 1945 (Box 34, Folder 498)
  - Tennessee - Gibson County - Yearly Report, 1929-1935; 1937; 1939-1940; 1943 and 1945 (Box 34, Folder 499)
  - Tennessee - Gibson County - Yearly Report, 1929-1935; 1937; 1939-1940; 1943 and 1945 (Box 34, Folder 500)
  - Tennessee - Gibson County - Yearly Report, 1929-1935; 1937; 1939-1940; 1943 and 1945 (Box 34, Folder 501)
  - Tennessee - Gibson County - Yearly Report, 1929-1935; 1937; 1939-1940; 1943 and 1945 (Box 34, Folder 502)
  - Tennessee - Gibson County - Yearly Report, 1929-1935; 1937; 1939-1940; 1943 and 1945 (Box 34, Folder 503)
  - Tennessee - Statistical Summaries, 1921-1946 (Box 34, Folder 504)
  - Tennessee - Sullivan County - Correspondence, February 21, 1930-December 29, 1934 (Box 34, Folder 505)
  - Tennessee - Sullivan County - Correspondence, January 11, 1935-October 4, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 506)
  - Tennessee - Sullivan County - Correspondence, January 11, 1935-October 4, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 507)
  - Tennessee - Sullivan County - Correspondence, January 11, 1935-October 4, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 508)
  - Tennessee - Sullivan County - Health Center Correspondence, December 18, 1935-November 3, 1949 (Box 35, Folder 509)
  - Tennessee - Sullivan County - Statistical Summaries, 1921-1950 (Box 35, Folder 510)
  - Tennessee - Sullivan County - Yearly Report, 1929-1935; 1937; 1939; 1941-1942; 1945 (Box 35, Folder 511)
  - Tennessee - Sullivan County - Yearly Report, 1929-1935; 1937; 1939; 1941-1942; 1945 (Box 35, Folder 512)
  - Tennessee - Sullivan County - Yearly Report, 1929-1935; 1937; 1939; 1941-1942; 1945 (Box 35, Folder 513)
  - Tennessee - Sullivan County - Yearly Report, 1929-1935; 1937; 1939; 1941-1942; 1945 (Box 35, Folder 514)
  - Tennessee - Sullivan County - Yearly Report, 1929-1935; 1937; 1939; 1941-1942; 1945 (Box 35, Folder 515)
  - Tennessee - Sullivan County - Yearly Report, 1929-1935; 1937; 1939; 1941-1942; 1945 (Box 35, Folder 516)
  - Tennessee - Sullivan County - Yearly Report, 1929-1935; 1937; 1939; 1941-1942; 1945 (Box 35, Folder 517)
  - Tennessee - Sullivan County - Yearly Report, 1929-1935; 1937; 1939; 1941-1942; 1945 (Box 35, Folder 518)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Correspondence and Reports, February 15, 1937-December 30, 1937 (Box 35, Folder 519)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Correspondence and Reports, February 9, 1937-November 23, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 520)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Correspondence and Reports, February 9, 1937-November 23, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 521)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Correspondence and Reports, February 9, 1937-November 23, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 522)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Correspondence and Reports, February 9, 1937-November 23, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 523)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Correspondence and Reports, February 9, 1937-November 23, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 524)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Correspondence and Reports, February 9, 1937-November 23, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 525)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Evaluation Schedules, 1947 and 1948 (Box 36, Folder 526)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Health Center Correspondence and Reports, January 18, 1944-December 19, 1947 (Box 36, Folder 527)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Health Center Correspondence and Reports, January 18, 1944-December 19, 1947 (Box 36, Folder 528)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Health Center Correspondence and Reports, January 18, 1944-December 19, 1947 (Box 36, Folder 529)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Health Center Correspondence and Reports, January 18, 1944-December 19, 1947 (Box 36, Folder 530)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Health Center Correspondence and Reports, January 18, 1944-December 19, 1947 (Box 36, Folder 531)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Health Center Correspondence and Reports, January 23, 1948-October 17, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 532)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Statistical Summaries, 1921-1949 (Box 37, Folder 533)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Tuberculosis Program Correspondence and Memoranda, February 11, 1949-August 7, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 534)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Tuberculosis Program Correspondence and Memoranda, February 11, 1949-August 7, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 535)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Tuberculosis Program Reports, July 1, 1939-June 30, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 536)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Tuberculosis Program Reports, July 1, 1939-June 30, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 537)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Tuberculosis Program Reports, July 1, 1939-June 30, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 538)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Yearly Report, 1938-1946 (Box 37, Folder 539)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Yearly Report, 1938-1946 (Box 37, Folder 540)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Yearly Report, 1938-1946 (Box 37, Folder 541)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Yearly Report, 1938-1946 (Box 37, Folder 542)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Yearly Report, 1938-1946 (Box 37, Folder 543)
  - Tennessee - University of Tennessee - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, May 15, 1930-June 12, 1938 (Box 37, Folder 544)
  - Tennessee - University of Tennessee - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, May 15, 1930-June 12, 1938 (Box 37, Folder 545)
  - Tennessee - University of Tennessee - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, May 15, 1930-June 12, 1938 (Box 37, Folder 546)
  - Tennessee - Vanderbilt University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, December 2, 1929-February 26, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 547)
  - Tennessee - Vanderbilt University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, December 2, 1929-February 26, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 548)
  - Tennessee - Vanderbilt University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, December 2, 1929-February 26, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 549)
  - Tennessee - Vanderbilt University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, December 2, 1929-February 26, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 550)
  - Tennessee - Vanderbilt University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, December 2, 1929-February 26, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 551)
  - Tennessee - Vanderbilt University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, December 2, 1929-February 26, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 552)
  - Tennessee - Vanderbilt University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, December 2, 1929-February 26, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 553)
  - Tennessee - Vanderbilt University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, December 2, 1929-February 26, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 554)
  - Tennessee - Whooping Cough Program - Correspondence and Reports, December 11, 1942-December 8, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 555)
  - Virginia - Richmond Department of Public Health - Medical Care for Indigents - Financial Statements, July 1, 1949-June 30, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 556)
  - Washington - Field Trip Reports, February 2, 1944-May 15, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 557)
  - Washington - General Correspondence and Memoranda, December 2, 1943-October 9, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 558)
- Public Health Fellowships, 3
  - Alabama - Postgraduate Medical (A-E), n.d. (Box 39, Folder 559)
  - Alabama - Postgraduate Medical (G-M), n.d. (Box 39, Folder 560)
  - Alabama - Postgraduate Medical (N-S), n.d. (Box 39, Folder 561)
  - Alabama - Postgraduate Medical (T-Z), n.d. (Box 39, Folder 562)
  - California - California Mental Health Institute (July 1-19, 1948) - Correspondence, June 25, 1948-September 21, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 563)
  - Fellowship Recipient Rosters - Alabama to Miscellaneous Fellowships, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 564)
  - Fellowship Recipient Rosters - Mississippi to Oklahoma, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 565)
  - Fellowship Recipient Rosters - Tennessee to Vermont, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 566)
  - Florida - Postgraduate Medical (C and H) (Box 39, Folder 567)
  - Kentucky - Laboratory Technicians (B-Y), n.d. (Box 39, Folder 568)
  - Kentucky - Postgraduate Medical (B-S), n.d. (Box 39, Folder 569)
  - Kentucky - Public Health Nursing (S), n.d. (Box 39, Folder 570)
  - Maine - Postgraduate Medical (A-D), n.d. (Box 39, Folder 571)
  - Maine - Postgraduate Medical (E-M), n.d. (Box 39, Folder 572)
  - Maine - Postgraduate Medical (N-T), n.d. (Box 39, Folder 573)
  - Maine - Undergraduate (M-W) (Box 39, Folder 574)
  - Massachusetts - Laboratory Technicians (B-G), n.d. (Box 40, Folder 575)
  - Massachusetts - Laboratory Technicians (H-J), n.d. (Box 40, Folder 576)
  - Massachusetts - Laboratory Technicians (M-R), n.d. (Box 40, Folder 577)
  - Massachusetts - Laboratory Technicians (S-W), n.d. (Box 40, Folder 578)
  - Massachusetts - Postgraduate Medical (A-C), n.d. (Box 40, Folder 579)
  - Massachusetts - Postgraduate Medical (D-H), n.d. (Box 40, Folder 580)
  - Massachusetts - Postgraduate Medical (K-M), n.d. (Box 40, Folder 581)
  - Massachusetts - Postgraduate Medical (N-R), n.d. (Box 40, Folder 582)
  - Massachusetts - Postgraduate Medical (S-W), n.d. (Box 40, Folder 583)
  - Massachusetts - Public Health Nursing (B-E), n.d. (Box 40, Folder 584)
  - Massachusetts - Public Health Nursing (F-L), n.d. (Box 40, Folder 585)
  - Massachusetts - Public Health Nursing (M-W), n.d. (Box 40, Folder 586)
  - Massachusetts - Undergraduate (A-B) (Box 41, Folder 587)
  - Massachusetts - Undergraduate (C-F) (Box 41, Folder 588)
  - Massachusetts - Undergraduate (G-K) (Box 41, Folder 589)
  - Massachusetts - Undergraduate (L-R) (Box 41, Folder 590)
  - Massachusetts - Undergraduate (S-Y) (Box 41, Folder 591)
  - Miscellaneous Fellowships - All States - Bacteriologists (F-S), n.d. (Box 41, Folder 592)
  - Miscellaneous Fellowships - All States - Health Officers (B-F), n.d. (Box 41, Folder 593)
  - Miscellaneous Fellowships - All States - Health Officers (H-P), n.d. (Box 41, Folder 594)
  - Miscellaneous Fellowships - All States - Health Officers (R-Z), n.d. (Box 41, Folder 595)
  - Miscellaneous Fellowships - All States - Public Health Nurses (B-P), n.d. (Box 41, Folder 596)
  - Miscellaneous Fellowships - All States - Sanitarians (A-F), n.d. (Box 41, Folder 597)
  - Miscellaneous Fellowships All States - Sanitarians (H-W), n.d. (Box 41, Folder 598)
  - Miscellaneous Fellowships All States - Survey of Undergraduate Fellowships, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 599)
  - Mississippi - Diagnosis of Cancer - Correspondence, June 30, 1947-October 16, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 600)
  - Mississippi - Laboratory Technicians (A-F), n.d. (Box 42, Folder 601)
  - Mississippi - Laboratory Technicians (H-P), n.d. (Box 42, Folder 602)
  - Mississippi - Laboratory Technicians (R-W), n.d. (Box 42, Folder 603)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (A-Be), n.d. (Box 42, Folder 604)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (Bi-By), n.d. (Box 42, Folder 605)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (C), n.d. (Box 42, Folder 606)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (D-E), n.d. (Box 42, Folder 607)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (F), n.d. (Box 42, Folder 608)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (G), n.d. (Box 42, Folder 609)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (Ha-He), n.d. (Box 42, Folder 610)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (Hi-J), n.d. (Box 43, Folder 611)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (K-L), n.d. (Box 43, Folder 612)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (M), n.d. (Box 43, Folder 613)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (N-P), n.d. (Box 43, Folder 614)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (R), n.d. (Box 43, Folder 615)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (Sa-Se), n.d. (Box 43, Folder 616)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (Sh-St), n.d. (Box 43, Folder 617)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (T-V), n.d. (Box 43, Folder 618)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (Wa-Will), n.d. (Box 43, Folder 619)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (Wils-Z), n.d. (Box 43, Folder 620)
  - Mississippi - Public Health Nursing (B-D), n.d. (Box 43, Folder 621)
  - Mississippi - Public Health Nursing (F-L), n.d. (Box 44, Folder 622)
  - Mississippi - Public Health Nursing (M-P), n.d. (Box 44, Folder 623)
  - Mississippi - Public Health Nursing (R-W), n.d. (Box 44, Folder 624)
  - Mississippi - Undergraduate (B) (Box 44, Folder 625)